-[frantic music playing]
-[panting]
-[ricochet pings]
[men grunt]
[fugitive panting]
[pounding]
-[gunshot]
-[music softens]
[man] Finish him off!
[fugitive panting]
[tense music playing]
[police siren blaring]
[man] Come on. hurry up!
-[gunshot echoes]
-[sirens. music fade]
[indistinct chatter]
-[gentle music playing]
-[dog barking faintly]
-Hey. Chiquinho.
-[Chiquinho] Morning. Stomper.
[music turns uplifting]
Morning. João. Is this mine?
Thanks. man.
Raimundo!
When are you going to train. Raimundo?
Just do it.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[music turns edgy]
[dry thuds]
[breathing in deeply]
[sighs]
[girl shouts] Hurry up. Toni!
Come on!
[music fades]
[gentle music returns]
[music turns unsettling]
Toni!
Come over here. Hurry!
Step away. Paulina. step away!
Just back up. Back up. please.
[music turns ominous]
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
[frenzied theme music playing]
WRATH
Focus on the fight. Júnior!
[taunting laugh]
[crowd roars]
Gotta raise your guard. man!
-Come on!
-You're a bitch.
[Toni] Gotta fight back!
-[crowd chants] Malamute! Malamute!
-[taunting laugh]
[crowd continues] Malamute!
[music stops]
[crowd chant echoes]
ADDRESS: FRANCISCO LOPES. 313
[distant sirens]
[ominous music playing]
[Paulina] Hey. There's no one in there.
Are you looking for Toni?
Antônio Trindade.
-Know where he is?
-At Malamute's fight.
Don't play around. Don't lose focus.
[electronic funk music playing]
You're weak!
[Toni] Yeah. Nice. kid!
You're a fucking loser.
No way you're winning this fight.
[crowd roars]
[growls] Come on. dammit!
You got him angry.
[grunts]
[Toni] Spin. spin! Yeah. that's it!
[coach] That's it. kid!
-Let's go.
-[Toni] Nah. why'd you get up?
Finish him. Come on!
He's taking too many risks.
[crowd roars]
[crowd chanting] Now you're dead!
Now you're dead!
Now you're dead! Now you're dead!
It's okay. He got him
when he was getting up. Goddamn.
[howling]
[Malamute] That's right!
I'm the fucking best!
This is fucking Trindade!
[whooping]
-Good job. Júnior. Nice fight.
-[Malamute] Trindade. that's right!
I am Malamute!
Fuck. yeah! Trindade for life!
Alright. Júnior. that's enough.
Knock it off.
Get down.
-[Malamute growls]
-[Toni] Nice fight.
What's wrong. Coach? I fucking won.
So tell me. were you fighting alone?
-Go pay your respects.
-[grunts]
Dammit. pay your respects
to your opponent.
Tank!
-Nice fight. Good job.
-[Tank] Thanks a lot. Good to see you.
-[Toni] Take it easy.
-[crowd chanting] Malamute! Malamute!
Act like a champion. You hear me?
Let me be one. fuck.
Why won't you let me fight Neco?
Let me take that guy.
Because fighting is here and here.
And here and here.
I need you to understand.
Then you can fight anyone you want.
Over here. Júnior.
What a great fight. Malamute!
Fantastic stuff.
You're coming for the belt. right?
Yeah. you bet I'm coming for the belt.
I'll be the new champion. Tell everybody.
And yo. everybody with a phone.
go on. start recording.
Yeah. whip it out right now.
Film everything and post it.
Neco the Thrasher. you're on my list. 'k?
You're gonna get the thrashing.
-I'll kick your ass.
-Alright. Stomper. He's a kid.
He's impossible is what he is.
Yeah. that's right. Malamute!
[microphone screech]
[crowd chanting] Malamute! Malamute!
[presenter] There you have it. The winner.
You're hot!
Babe! You saw? You saw me win?
Yeah! I crossed the whole city
to come see you.
-I drained the Tank!
-[chuckles]
Hey. great fight. Malamute.
I know how to take a loss when it's fair.
Thanks. Mrs. Yana.
Sorry I hurt your fighter. I was just…
No problem. it's fine.
You were just doing your job.
-Let's go.
-No hard feelings.
Hey. when do I get to see you fight again?
I remember your hammer kick. Incredible.
We miss your fights.
-Thank you.
-Come on.
[sighs]
[Yana] Toni…
Congrats.
[Toni grunts]
[indistinct chatter]
[ominous music playing]
[man] Catch you later. man. take care.
[coach] Stomper. Take it easy!
-All good. man.
-Hey. there's Toni. Go talk to the guy.
You ran away from the hospital?
What do you want from me?
I wanna say thanks.
-The doctor said you saved my life.
-No need to.
And you should thank the doctor and God.
Hey. man. you took a bullet
right in the head. You shoulda croaked.
Alright. man. see you later.
God bless you.
Do you know who I am? Marcelo Lazarus.
You wrote that when you filled this out.
You don't know your own name?
No.
Did you lose your memory?
Okay…
You listen here.
I thought someone
had dumped a corpse in the landfill.
Turns out it was you.
You kept repeating that name.
Marcelo.
Lazarus. I wrote it in
because it comes from the Bible.
You were as good as dead. man.
I honor God through my actions.
That's why I took you outta there.
[somber music continues]
May God light your way. son.
[music intensifies. fades]
TRINDADE FIGHT ACADEMY
[fan whirring]
BIBLE
[Toni] "Commit thy way unto the Lord."
"Trust also in Him."
"And He shall answer."
[somber music resumes]
[inhales shakily]
MUNICIPAL HOSPITAL
[seagulls squawking]
[somber music continues]
PATIENT: MARCELO LAZARUS
[Toni] Morning. Laércio!
[Laércio] Morning!
FIGHTING GYM
[bangs. thuds]
[upbeat samba music playing]
What's going on. Olívia?
There he is! There's the winner.
Morning. How are ya doing?
-Hiya doing. All good?
-[Olívia laughs]
Saw the video. Nice going.
Yeah. man. the guy thought
he'd beat you. You showed him.
-That was nice.
-Yeah. well my head is pounding like hell.
So you can dish it out
but you can't take it. Malamute.
-[scoffs] Just a hungover. That's all.
-[Olívia] Ha!
Partied hard. you know?
I should get to enjoy myself.
-Am I right?
-Yeah. sure.
To be honest. should take the day off.
I know your coach
and he won't go easy on you if you do.
'Cause MMA is serious business.
You represent Trindade. don't forget.
-Yeah.
-[phone ringing]
You go ahead.
I really gotta take this call.
-Come train though.
-Sure. I'll see you there later.
-You listen. Júnior.
-[ringing continues]
If you hurt my friend. you'll regret it.
So. watch it.
-Don't you think of it.
-[ringing continues]
Mrs. Yana.
[Yana] I'd like us
to keep the conversation going.
I'd like to work with you.
to boost your career.
Uh…
I don't know. I'm still thinking.
Júnior. listen.
It's take it or leave it. alright?
-[upbeat samba music playing]
-[horn toots]
♪ Inside my X1 ♪
-[hearty chuckle]
-♪ Inside my X1 ♪
Yeah. yeah.
Hey. Olívia! He finally won!
See that?
Did you see the fight last night?
-Morning. how are ya?
-Morning.
[coach] Nice shades! Lovely.
-Thanks. found a great vendor.
-[coach laughs]
-You guys are early for a change.
-[driver] Yeah. I guess so.
Good morning!
[Toni] Hey!
Good morning. Master!
-[Toni] Morning.
-[Olívia chuckles]
[Toni] Good morning.
[Olívia] Good morning. Coach.
-So I heard Malamute won?
-[Toni] Yeah. you heard that?
Showed him how we do it!
That was yesterday.
Get over it. Today is another day.
Back to training.
We don't want you getting soft.
I'm serious.
If you want a cuddle. get a puppy.
Come on. fight. dammit!
[coach] That's it. Nice.
Create space. come on.
Make room. Catolé! Fuck's sake.
Hey kid. your stance is awful. Come on.
[coach] That's it. Underneath.
You gotta block that.
-[Toni] That's it. that's it!
-[coach] You gotta be quick.
[Toni] Keep moving. keep it up.
Leg. legs! Yes! That's it. Nice.
-Hello!
-[coach] That's it.
-[woman] Hey. Dad.
-[coach] Good!
Hey. sweetheart.
-[coach] That's it. She's bigger than you.
-Hey!
-Look at me. You gotta raise that elbow.
-[woman] You got this. Olívia!
[coach] Don't let her body-lock you.
Defend yourself! Yes!
Don't give her any space.
Quick. You gotta move fast.
How's it going?
As usual. Rushing around.
Hey. sweetie. Where's your boyfriend?
Can't find your fighter?
-This look like a daycare to you?
-He's not my responsibility.
I only have one child.
That's one too many.
-Where is he? Lunchtime!
-[Olívia] Time to eat. guys.
Give me a minute. okay?
Hey. Gabi. where's my stew at? This one?
-Yeah.
-Got chicken?
No. not today. sorry.
Whose blood is that there?
Whose damn blood is that?
Catolé.
Don't try to deny it. Catolé.
If that's your blood.
who needs to clean it?
Coach. it's me.
Then get off your ass and come do it. son.
Please clean up your own freaking blood.
I'll do it after lunch. alright?
Just cut me some slack.
I'll break that face for real.
You better go clean up that blood now.
Then you can eat.
-[Gabi] Way to go to humiliate him. Dad.
-[Catolé] Fucking bullshit.
Hey. uh. who's that homeless guy
by the door?
[resigned] Yeah.
[drumroll]
[Toni] Your all. do it with speed!
-Almost done. Push through.
-[coach] Let's go. Catolé.
Hang in there. Just a bit more.
[Toni] Pick it up. come on!
Twenty seconds to the end
of the third round. You got this. okay?
This is a drill. Catolé. Hurry.
Don't think. Power through and it's over.
That's it. Nice.
-Get in there.
-[coach] Move. Catolé.
[Toni] Yes. good!
[coach] Don't overthink.
Be quick.
Good job.
Nicely done. team. You all did great.
Alright. gather round.
[coach] Everyone in the ring.
It's never gonna be easy.
Right. Hammer?
Damn straight.
Not for one day.
It's gonna hurt.
We bleed doing this.
Isn't that right. Catolé? Hmm?
Anyone here wanna stop?
Hmm?
-It's in these moments of pain…
-[emotive music playing softly]
…that we've got to read the fucking signs.
Because God…
God has a purpose
for each and every one of us.
Thing is. we gotta do our part.
Because you gotta fight.
Don't ever give up.
Fight!
Nobody wins without fighting.
Alright. thank you for today.
-Well said. Good job everyone.
-All did great.
-Alright. On three!
-[all] Let's go!
One. two. three. Trindade. fuck yeah!
[Toni] Nice!
[overlapping clamor]
[Toni] Olívia.
-What's up. Coach?
-Check it out.
I got a client for you.
HER CUT
-[Olívia] What happened to you?
-[Toni clears throat] It was a robbery.
-He got lucky.
-Yeah.
He better get it
checked out though. right?
He's fine. It's just a scratch. Olívia.
How do you know this guy?
He's my cousin
from our village in the country.
[Olívia] Ah.
-And does he ever talk? Your cousin?
-Olívia. please. Give it a rest.
Alright.
-I'll use the razor.
-[metallic clink]
[strident music playing]
-[Toni] Hey. hey. hey!
-What are you doing? Stop it!
Calm down. calm down.
Hey. no one's
trying to hurt you here. right?
Let go of her arm. Let go!
Calm down. calm down.
I'm sorry. Olívia.
He just got out of the hospital.
He's still confused.
[threatening music playing]
Sorry. miss.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
We'll use a clipper. alright?
[buzzing]
-[funky music playing]
-[motor droning]
[horns beeping]
You paying for
two license plates. asshole? Seriously.
Olívia. do you think you can remind Hammer
to remove all that debris
in front of the gym?
It's gathering termites.
and it's a safety hazard.
[music continues]
[Alpha coach] Alright.
speed and intensity. Let's go!
Yes! Nice. kid!
My warrior!
[music continues over speakers]
[coach] Back. back. Concentrate.
Hey. Júnior?
-You alright?
-Yeah. How are you?
Oss.
-What do you think of this place?
-It's fire.
-[Yana chuckles]
-Fuck. man. it's awesome. Shit. sorry.
Don't worry about that.
What's the verdict? Your decision?
You know now?
There's an ongoing feud
between Alpha Rio and Trindade. yeah?
[Yana] It's between Toni and my dad.
Their rivalry doesn't involve me.
It doesn't involve you either.
I don't want to hurt Toni.
Alpha Rio is just me. I swear. Okay?
You gotta think about yourself.
What do you want?
Who do you want to be?
You wanna stick with shitty fights?
You over it?
You wanna fight Neco The Thrasher?
Fine! Let's do it!
I know I can crush the guy. fuck yeah.
[Yana] Yes! Of course. I want a belt.
And you'll get one for me.
[Malamute laughs]
You in?
-Say it.
-[Malamute] Yes.
Yo. what's up. little worm?
-[Malamute chuckles]
-Go fuck yourself!
-Come here. Come on. you twat!
-Tank…
[jeering laugh]
[traffic bustle]
You told her I'm your cousin.
Why though?
Should I have said
I found you in the trash?
Look. we don't want people
to start talking.
I don't want any rumors about you.
If there's a price on your head.
my bet is
they're gonna want to finish the job.
Hey there. Marcelo!
You look great! What did you do. Toni?
He even looks like a real fighter now.
He doesn't fight. I do!
Here. let's see what you got. Fireball.
-[Paulina] It's on!
-Yeah. Stomper against Fireball!
Wait. whoa. hang on.
Slow down. Take it easy. Paulina! Ow!
Stop! Stop. please!
You win. you win. I'm out! Jesus!
-Hey. girl. you're really strong.
-[chanting] Paulina!
You're even showing your teeth now.
Come on. the two of us.
Not now. Paulina. You're late
for your tutoring and you know it.
-Admit it. You think I'd win.
-Course I do. Go on.
[laughs]
-[Toni] Next time. I'll win.
-Yeah. we'll see.
[Toni] I'm gonna train.
[traffic bustle]
The bus here will take you
to the bus station.
Here. take this cash.
And get as far away
from here as you can. kid.
'Cause you need to go start over.
This is a gift from the heart. okay?
Just take it.
-Do it.
-Where should I go?
[Hammer] Stomper!
Didi showed up at the gym.
She's trying to stir up some shit.
Come on!
Ah. fuck me.
Shit. Alright. let's go. Come with us.
[tense music playing]
-[Toni] What the hell is this?
-[man] Wanna help?
Help you? How dare you. This is my stuff.
Who do you think you are?
Untie my stuff now!
Uh. uh. uh. uh…
Five months. Antônio.
You haven't paid an installment
in five months.
Not even interest.
Patience has its limits.
Don't you know that?
Alright. Didi.
It's all I've got for now.
Toni…
You and I go way back.
I know you really well
and I know you're lying.
Come on. let's go. Didi.
You think you can give me orders?
What's wrong with you?
You're not getting out of what you owe.
Didi.
Malamute has got a fight coming up.
Pays really well.
I know it won't cover all of it.
but it's money. and it'll be yours.
But I need all of my equipment
in order to train him.
Don't fucking get near her!
[Toni] Stop. Marcelo! Stop!
-Stand back!
-[man] You wanna die?
-[Didi] Easy.
-[Toni] Relax. Marcelo.
You're crazy. dammit.
[buzzing]
Load. come on. Let's get outta here.
[man] Got you nervous. huh?
If you keep your word for real.
I'll return it all. Promise.
Your guy better win. you hear?
[sly chuckle]
[Toni] Marcelo.
Calm down.
[music playing from inside bar]
[motor revs]
Sorry.
[Malamute] Alright… now!
[in Portuguese] ♪ I know
You don't want my love anymore ♪
♪ I know you ♪
♪ Don't love me anymore ♪
♪ I know I'm not
Who you always dreamed of ♪
♪ But I'll win your love back ♪
♪ All for myself ♪
♪ Oh. Gabriela ♪
[Malamute] Hey!
♪ Her ♪
[out-of-tune vocalizing]
[crowd cheering. clapping]
We need to talk.
Make some noise! Fucking Alpha Rio!
[Tank roars]
What the fuck is this?
Yeah. well I thought
you were working late tonight.
No. I mean you hanging out
with these fucking dicks?
Oh my God. relax. Gabi.
You know I'm still gonna fight Tank
in the ring. so what's the fucking issue?
-I don't even like these jokers.
-Yeah. it really showed on stage just now.
You know I saw you walk into Alpha.
-Well. it was to check the place out.
-Hey! You think I'm an idiot. Júnior?
I don't believe a word you're saying.
You're lying.
I told you.
I went to check the place out. That's all.
Yeah. With all your training gear.
[sighs]
You know no one at Trindade
can match your fighting skills. right?
Yeah.
I'm not kidding. Júnior.
And I'm not saying it to flatter you.
I'm not your mother.
you can do whatever you want.
Understand?
Hey. look at me.
I'll explain everything to your dad.
-For now. can we please just chill?
-I am chill.
-Come on.
-Yeah. no. I'm chill. but I'm not kidding.
-Go hang out with your buddies.
-What's wrong with you?
Quit messing around.
I'm going home.
-Hey. Gabi.
-Just stop.
[Tank] Come on. Malamute.
Let's sing another one.
What's up. man? Don't worry about it.
She's just being a chick.
Go. play another one.
[intriguing music playing]
TONI "STOMPER" FIGHTS FOR HIS FIRST TITLE
JACKHAMMER IS THE CHAMP!
[door opens]
[door closes]
Here. take some for your head.
Is that you?
[music fades]
Uh-huh.
Used to be me.
Goddamn. this light is fucked.
Fucking shit.
You can crash here
at the gym tonight. okay?
But tomorrow you're gonna have to leave.
[unsettling music playing]
[strident shrill tone plays]
Get some sleep.
It's late.
Hey. I know you were
trying to help me earlier.
But forget about it.
It's not worth fighting over. okay?
[footsteps fade]
[Toni] Forgetting sometimes is a blessing.
[knocking]
[Olívia] Hello! Good morning!
[Catolé] Morning. boss!
[insistent knocking]
-[Catolé] Open up!
-[insistent banging]
[Marcelo groans]
-[Catolé] Hello?
-[knocking]
[Olívia] Good morning!
For those of you who don't know.
this is Marcelo.
I'm the one who cut his hair.
Let's get this day started. Come on. guys.
Wait. Who is that guy?
No idea. He's been around here.
You didn't notice?
Whoa!
-Girl. damn. you have magic hands.
-Of course I do.
I can do some magic on your face too.
Don't test me.
-What the fuck?
-[edgy music playing]
[Catolé] What happened?
There's no mat. no bag.
What's going on here?
Yeah. and BOB. Where's BOB?
Do you know anything about this?
[sighs. clicks teeth]
Alright. well since you're here.
give me a hand.
We'll grab the old punching bag.
Come on.
Listen. brother. you should stick with me.
I'm the top dog here at Trindade. alright?
You a champion?
Um. no. But I think
you know Malamute. Malamute.
Yeah.
Well. I'm a better fighter.
I think Júnior'd like to know that.
-How about I tell him?
-Shit! Don't you make jokes about that.
-Hey. sorry I'm late. Good morning.
-[Olívia] Good morning.
Morning. Coach! Tell us the truth.
You had a fire sale yesterday?
How about you stop talking
and start training?
How do we do that without any equipment?
I found this old thing in the back.
You got legs. right?
And arms as well. son?
So quit whining.
And get to work.
What's up. family?
Look what I found.
This old punching dummy.
-The so-called BOB.
-[Olívia] Did it have to be that ugly?
It's ugly.
It's hideous.
Then it'll be easier to beat. Look.
-Where the hell is Malamute?
-Maybe they took him with your stuff.
Can't catch a break. for fuck's sakes.
Alright. get the old mat out here then.
Hey. since you're here. son.
you might as well give us a hand. right?
Thanks.
[edgy fun music playing]
[Catolé hissing]
Are you starving or something?
Why aren't you
punching the bag any harder?
With all due respect. Coach.
it's way too old to use.
If I punch it. it'll explode.
Then destroy it. goddammit!
Punch it for real!
[violent thud]
Harder!
Come on!
[Toni clears throat]
Don't laugh.
[comic jazz twist]
[upbeat jazz samba playing]
[Hammer] Yeah. that's good.
Looking light. Let it fall.
Got it?
[Toni] Off the ropes.
out of the corner. That's it.
Stomper. hey. All good?
You know. sometimes we get up
on the wrong foot.
Don't worry. Stomper. It'll get better.
-Let's go!
-Come on. guys. move it. Move it!
-What's up. Dad?
-Hey. sweetie. How you doing?
-You alright?
-[Gabi] Yeah.
More movement. kid.
Punch him!
-Punch him! Two. one-two.
-What happened to all the equipment?
[inhales]
[sighs] Ah…
Well. I had bills to pay.
That simple. So I sold some stuff.
Just your dad
being your dad. I'll sort it out.
Move! Fuck. lift your guard. please!
What the hell you doing?
Didn't you hear him?
-Keep moving.
-[Hammer] Hands up. dammit!
-Dad. when that happens--
-[Toni] Nah. what is this?
If you keep fighting like that.
you'll be a sack of potatoes.
You'll get thrown right to the ground!
-Wake up!
-Dad. look at me.
When you've got these issues.
let me know. We can sort it together.
[sighs] It's my problem. sweetheart.
Could you cut me some slack today?
I'll sort this out.
Malamute's got a fight soon.
Prize money is good.
He's ready for it. He'll win.
[sighs deeply]
Well. Malamute's not
with Trindade anymore.
Truth is. I saw him going into Alpha.
[muffled buzzing]
Hey! Cover for me. Hammer.
You got it. Coach.
-I can give you a ride--
-Don't follow me please!
[thuds]
[Alpha coach] Yes. good.
Malamute!
You enjoying your new gym?
-I was gonna tell you.
-Yeah. I bet you were.
I bet you were gonna tell me.
When I started training you.
you were 15.
and just skin and bone. like a twig.
You thought you were a tough guy.
involved in drug dealing.
You were headed for a wall.
You think you did good?
Is this fair to you? Hmm?
Is that it?
I signed you up for a fight. Malamute.
People are depending on you.
I don't know how you sleep at night.
you fucking traitor.
I'm not a traitor. Toni.
-Oh. no?
-No. I made a decision for me is all.
For you. It's all you think about.
It's all about you.
You ungrateful. selfish asshole.
-What did you say?
-You're ungrateful. Ungrateful.
-Ungrateful?
-That's what you are.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Oh. yeah? Was I ungrateful
when I took your wasted ass home
all those times
you got totally hammered at the bar?
And was I a dickhead
all those times I took care
of your daughter when she was sick?
-You failed even as a father. fuck.
-You shut your…
No. I'm speaking the truth!
-Shut your fucking mouth!
-What the fuck are you gonna do. huh?
If we fight right now.
I'll crush your fucking ass.
-You drunken old fool!
-Watch it--
[breathing heavily]
Go for it!
Go for it. fuck!
[breathing heavily]
You're not a kid anymore.
You're a grown-ass man now.
You know what you're doing.
You think you got me angry at you?
You think I'm fucking upset with you?
No!
No. I'm upset with myself!
'Cause I didn't raise you
to be a man. I failed you.
Your values are awful.
You've got no honor as a fighter.
So I'm angry with me!
I came to look you in the eyes.
And to bless you.
Okay? It's fine. You live your life.
I won't get in your way.
don't worry. Okay?
I hope to God things go well for you.
May God watch over you
and light your path.
[shaky breathing. inhales]
[whispers] And you…
You are exactly like your father.
[drumroll]
[Hammer] You gotta move.
Don't leave your head still.
[edgy jazz music playing]
[Hammer] Movement is the secret.
Your target's easy to hit.
-Good job. kid.
-[Catolé chuckles] Look at the newbie.
Think you're a big shot already. huh?
Let's partner. You in?
Five minutes. We'll take it easy. alright?
Catolé. will you leave him alone?
Don't worry. Olívia. I'll go easy.
Come on!
Get up here.
Come on up! Am I talking to a wall
or something? Let's go.
Hey. I'll give you an advantage.
A hand behind my back. okay?
-Are you ready?
-Don't hurt him. alright?
Don't worry. man. It won't hurt at all.
Fight!
Good one. Stay sharp. bro.
[Hammer] Raise those hands!
[Catolé] Yeah. that's it.
Come to the middle.
-[Olívia] Goddamn!
-[Hammer] Catolé.
Better use two hands
or you're fucked! [chuckles]
-Sorry about that.
-[Catolé] Don't say sorry.
Fight like a man.
[crashing thud]
That was damn good.
What's wrong?
You're dead. motherfucker.
[Catolé groaning]
-[Hammer] What?
-What was that?
[Olívia] Catolé. you're really dense. huh?
I told you not to fight the guy.
[Hammer] What the hell. Catolé?
What's wrong with you?
-[Catolé] My wrist…
-Pick yourself up.
-Gabi. come out!
-[Catolé] Hurts bad.
[Olívia] Fuck. it's broken.
Why did you do that?
[Catolé] Ow!
-[Olívia] Calm down.
-[Gabi] Dammit. Catolé.
My dad's gonna fucking kill you!
[distant sirens]
[sinister music playing]
[panting heavily]
[music intensifies]
-[music fades]
-[heavy panting]
[wolf whistle]
You're ambidextrous?
Hmm. First this. then the other.
Got it?
[Marcelo] Yeah.
[Gabi] You're strong.
but you're pretty clumsy.
I'll show you this.
just this once. It's simple.
Jab. jab. dodge the straight.
cross. straight. uppercut.
[rhythmic beat]
Follow the rhythm.
Firm stance. [gloves slam]
Jab. jab. dodge the straight.
Nice.
Good.
Firm stance.
That's it.
Go. Marcelo.
Good!
Nice.
That's good.
[Gabi laughs]
[Marcelo grunts]
[pants]
You got it.
Hmm.
[emotive music playing]
Ever break your nose?
[grunts]
You got that from a fight. right?
I got one too. look.
See that?
[grunts]
Hmm. But that wasn't from a fight though.
You been lying?
Who are you?
And what are you doing here?
-What are you after?
-[clank]
He confuses fighting
with brawling. that's all.
He wants to fight. but he's green.
Well. even if he's green.
he still crushed Catolé sparring.
I didn't mean to hurt him.
[Toni] Hurt him how?
No big deal. just the wrist…
It's really not too bad. A fracture…
[Toni] His wrist?
What?
Just what I fucking needed.
I thought it couldn't get any worse.
Fuck me! I just lost
that asshole Malamute.
Now I lose Catolé
because you were sparring?
This is bullshit.
Oh. I swear to God. [groans]
Let me fight then.
I'll replace Malamute.
[gentle music playing]
'Cause if I'm here right now.
it's because God put me on your path.
[Gabi] Dad. you missed it.
but you should've seen it.
Catolé couldn't get a punch in.
This guy's got instinct and reflexes.
He's clumsy for now.
with his legs mostly. We can fix that.
The only thing I'm sure of
is I'm a fighter.
Nah. he's not a fighter.
I want you out of here by tomorrow.
[music fades]
Catolé's hurt.
Better not forget about that.
His replacement's right here.
Come on. get in.
Come on. dude. let's get back to it.
IF YOU'RE NOT A COACH.
NO ADVICE!
[Toni] Watch it. That's it.
Good. Keep moving.
[Catolé hissing]
-[Toni] How you feeling?
-Fine.
-Quicker. alright?
-Got it.
Practice on me.
Good. nice.
That's it. you got it.
-[Catolé hisses. grunts]
-[Toni] Yeah.
[pained grunt]
[grunts in pain]
You good enough to fight. Catolé?
All good. trust me. Coach. I'm fine.
-You're fine. but can you fight. Catolé?
-[breathless] I can. Yes. I can.
I just need good bandages
and to warm up real good.
Trust me. Coach.
[ominous music playing]
[Toni yells]
[Hammer] Are you good?
[Toni exhales]
[sighs]
[crowd roars]
-That got you good!
-I wanna bet. How do I do that?
-You need cash. bro. that's all.
-Well. to be honest. I'm broke.
You got a pretty nice watch.
-Oh. yeah? Only valuable thing I got.
-I'll give you 300. Pays 3 to 1.
-Alright. now get lost.
-Okay.
Poor motherfucker.
[intriguing music playing]
[music fades]
[ominous buzz]
[frenzied music playing]
[music stops]
You sure. Stomper?
Wagner's a big deal. you know.
He's almost as experienced as you are.
Thing is he's 15 years younger than you.
It's a big risk.
You with me or against me on this?
Dude. I'm always with you.
-Then act like it. damn it.
-Dad.
What's going on?
You know what's going on. Fights on.
-Take 'em off.
-No. don't listen to her.
-[Gabi] Take them off.
-Continue.
-It's happening.
-Do it. Take those off!
Yeah. if I don't fight. who will?
[presenter] Representing Trindade Academy.
Marcelo Lazarus!
[pop music playing over loudspeakers]
Wagner's real good.
He hits hard. he's strong.
You gotta be patient. alright?
Guard always up. protect your face.
Wait for the right moment.
Just wait for it. Got it?
Don't forget. kid.
This is MMA. it's not street fighting.
Get in there.
[presenter] And in the other corner.
Wagner…
the Earthquake!
[crowd roars]
Yeah! Come on!
[ref] You know the rules.
Always follow my commands
and respect each other.
Touch gloves now.
To your corners.
You ready? You ready?
Now fight!
You gotta move. Marcelo.
Gotta move. You're not a post. fuck.
Keep your goddamned hands up!
[spectator] Let's go! Yeah!
[Toni] Raise your hands!
Move. move. come on!
[crowd chanting] Ooh. he'll kill you!
[Toni] Keep your guard up.
[chanting] Ooh. he'll kill you!
Ooh. he'll kill you!
[Toni] Nice!
Focus on the fight. Focus!
[Hammer] Holy shit!
-[Toni] Make some space!
-[coach] Make space. Wagner!
That's it!
[Toni] Dammit! Spin around.
That's it! Now get up!
We shouldn't have let him fight. Hammer.
Come on. Marcelo! You gotta move more!
It's over for him. fuck.
-[shrill buzzing]
-[Toni] Protect your head!
You gotta do something. Wake up!
[buzzing intensifies]
[Gabi. muffled] Marcelo!
Move. Marcelo!
-[buzzing stops]
-[Wagner yells]
[Hammer] Mount him! Yes!
You got it!
[Toni] Go. now! That's it. crush him!
-[Hammer] Destroy him.
-[Toni] Keep working.
[Hammer] It's now or never.
Marcelo! Hit him! Hit him!
Yes. good.
[Hammer] Yes. that's it!
-[Toni] Don't let up.
-[Hammer] Crush him!
[distorted growls]
[shrill buzzing]
-Stop. it's over!
-[ref] Stop!
-Stop. stop!
-No!
Get off!
[Marcelo yells]
It's over! Enough! Enough!
It's over. Marcelo.
-[Marcelo yells]
-[Toni] Fight's over. Marcelo.
It's done. It's over. you hear? Hey. hey…
It's over. All done.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[closing theme music playing]
[music stops]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-